Hello, I'm Hiker CP.
I'm here now.
(I don't know where
the nest is either.
..) East Java
I am now south
of the equator.
The place I've always
wanted to be.
The most famous volcano in
Java is the Blue Volcano.
I'm going to see the two blue
volcanoes in Indonesia.
We've arrived on the first day,
please watch the VCR.
I'll exchange it for
a hundred dollars.
（Our guide for the trip,
Han Sheng, is an overseas Chinese from Surabaya,
Indonesia.
(First day at the airport,
check in to the hotel) (The team member just got off the plane said he didn't bring any shoes,
and the tour guide bought a pair on the spot!)
(Going to Sai Mo Waterfalls) Supermarkets
actually have freshly brewed coffee.
I heard that there is a restaurant in Xinyi District (?).
（"Anyone ever had one?)
（Today is (day2) we are going
to the middle of East Java.
It's located at a place
called Seibu Falls,
which is said to be a volcano.
The erosion of the place feels very,
very spectacular.
"A lot of waterfalls.
" That's what this place looks like.
It's really hard to get there. As you can see,
basically.
Right in the middle
of the rainforest.
The Wilderness Traveler explores
this part of Indonesia because
They say they're the only
ones who run this route,
so I was going to do it myself.
I'm sorry I took the bus,
but I could have rented a car,
and then I found this side.
Transportation is really,
really bad. We'll have to charter a car.
A chartered car is too
expensive for me alone.
So, since we rarely go
with a tour, let's
see if we're going with
a tour this time.
It should be convenient
because we were
taken care of all day yesterday.
The last time I was in Indonesia
was 18 years ago.
The place on the left
is called Banda Aceh.
Indonesia is the worst
place in the tsunami.
The Red Cross came here
to do school work,
sort of reconstruction and education.
Sevu Falls is out of here,
dog! Crew!
Currently, there's
an observation deck
and a parking lot here
at Sauvoo Falls.
Tumpak means there's
a stack.
（The waterfalls are more like it,
but I've been here before.
（"It doesn't look like this." "And then,
the more customers.)
(The more he builds,
the more he exaggerates.
) Taiwan's Pingxi!
Very waterfall,
Indonesian version! Feeling
up for an Indonesian climb?
Go down to the bottom
of the waterfall.
Wear your basis sandals now.
(Wear sandals as you will be
treading water) All the way
down Usually this attraction
is in mainland China.
There would be a cable car,
but this is Indonesia, so there isn't,
so you can take the cable car down.
I've been waiting for
almost five minutes,
and they're still in the race.
The reason for the racecars.
Down here,
you can also take this waterway.
This side is all waterfalls
Taroko Canyon (？？？？)
Because the waterfalls are in the back,
all very much like in ....
It's raining. I was just looking
at the waterfall from up there.
Let's wait, let's take a
bridge and go swimming.
Rainbow! Triathlon picker! Checking
out the terrain now!
Where's the best place to go
for a swim? The return trip,
it's a race to the top.
Indonesia 101 Race
Pineapple Durian
It's kind of like sweet sugarcane.
Snakeberries. Can we talk about this?
You can pick up snakeberries on the road (there are many on the roadside,
you don't have to buy them).
Ten thousand NT dollars
for a stretch of road,
eighteen NT dollars from Shengguang
to the vegetable garden
My little hands have nowhere to grab!
I'm using all my abs right now!
The vegetable garden is connected
to a convenient
house! Now I'm leaning
forward completely.
(Lunch was at a restaurant after the waterfall, which was quite Chinese
-style.)
Is it spicy? (This is okay.
) (Not as spicy as yesterday.)
You get a cute little flag (Why did
I encounter a Pokémon
- Scorpion!)
I almost threw up after
driving on a very
bumpy mountain road
to the Bromo Hotel.
And I have a slight headache. The
temperature is quite cold now,
around ten degrees Celsius.
I felt too tired and the shaking was too much,
so I didn't eat.
Motion sickness medication,
and we're currently at an altitude of 2100 meters,
so we're being driven directly to 2100 meters.
Bromo (I couldn't finish it,
so I just ordered stir
-fried vegetables).
Because we need to leave
very early tomorrow,
around 2:00 AM, it should be...
Climbing mountains in the dark is a bit
like climbing mountains in Taiwan.
If all goes well,
we'll come back for breakfast.
Songxuelou doesn't
have air conditioning,
so it should have hot water.
We need to take a jeep to
Bromo's viewpoint
at 3 AM to secure a good spot.
The room was very warm
and comfortable,
pretty cool, and there was a Jeep.
Super crowded
looks
What's wrong? You seem upset.
(Everyone's so sleepy zzzzz)
The scene of illegal parking in Wuling
XDDD Everyone parked on the highway
Stop on the left and right,
line up in a row, basically cramming this side in. If you want to get up here,
this is...
Jeep and horse
roasting corn!
We are currently at the observation
deck; sunrise is at 5:30 AM.
It's quite scary; there
are no railings here,
so please be careful not to fall.
You can buy some hot food here.
It's actually quite
similar to Wuling,
where there are many people.
Wuling. Wuling is a place to
chase snow and sunrises,
and here's the Wuling Archway—that's
where everyone looks.
We're here to see the
sunrise at Qilai (??).
We shouldn't eat
such terrible food.
And we have extra eggs,
so it's only 15,
000 Indonesian Rupiah.
Eating instant noodles
on the mountain
is so satisfying! It
only costs 30 NTD.
At an altitude of 2,
400 meters, the sunrise occurred
while eating instant noodles.
It wasn't too cold because
of the altitude of 2,
400 meters, so I felt okay.
I wore [something] today.
A wool base layer followed by a static mid
-layer vest
Add a Kawas lightest down jacket
and a GORE
-TEX shirt.
The feeling of sunrise amidst
the sea of clouds
This place has a kind of ink painting
feel to it (it's amazing!!)
What is the smoke? Is it from a volcano? (Yes,
it's from a volcano!) Volcanic ash.
The volcano behind it is
erupting and exploding!
(Volcanic smoke keeps
billowing out!) Saying
goodbye to Bromo volcano
was really awesome!
It sprayed out,
it ejaculated! But now it's stopped.
Let me repeat that here,
behind us is Semeru.
Ahead is Kerilo (Batók volcano),
and this is where it's erupting.
Bromo keeps spewing.
We should be at the bottom
of the volcano soon.
The photo was taken from the same spot where my feet were,
both when I was riding a Jeep there and now.
The people had mostly dispersed,
and the atmosphere had become quite warm.
If you come by yourself, you must hire a car,
so this time I'm going with...
The tour itinerary for chartered cars
is different from what we used to do.
I want to do it myself (as a backpacker),
but it's just too inconvenient.
We traveled from Saiwu
Falls yesterday
to Mount Bromo today.
Now, we need to hire a Jeep to go to
the crater of Mount Ijen tomorrow.
The itinerary was specially arranged
because this place was just here.
I asked the guide and he said there
are absolutely no public buses.
There should usually be small towns where
you can hitch a ride up to Bromo,
but...
Without this,
there was no Saiwu Falls yesterday,
no bus, no public transport.
We need to hire a car,
so we went with a travel agency.
It's very convenient to travel
with wilderness travelers, OK?
Now I'm going to Wuling
Archway to catch a Jeep
(haha (the ink painting
is really beautiful)).
You can see Bromo is yelling
at us as we walk
down from the South Lake
Vegetable Garden (?).
I don't know where it is,
but it's probably one by one.
Hiss... Oh wow,
that sounds like a sound effect! (It's
real! It's not a sound effect.)
Are we going to take
this horse? To the
volcano? I'm not sure either.
Anyway, we're in a very
desolate place now.
Then all of them were Jeep cars,
it looked like a movie scene.
The one with lots of special effects
(I'm talking about Mad Max!).
They will lead you by the horse,
and then this...
(Can't we add more whips? ~~~)
Adding whips costs extra xddd
I almost got a cramp
(I was terrified).
I was so nervous I thought
I was going to fall.
This core core
eruption
You just need to put on the
front half of the shoe.
Because you need to be
ready to pull yourself
out at any time when you're
about to fall.
Just like with carding shoes! Just
place the card where you want it.
Is riding on horseback good? My
brother is giving me a ride.
I was also born in the
Year of the Horse,
and he is now...
I've never ridden a horse before,
even at a 7/10 pace.
Bro~~~ Brother Ma,
don't go astray (A real horse
expert!!! So handsome!)
(Princess Pearl rode away~~)
It sways up and down so
you won't fall off;
you can't resist it.
You need to go back
and use its force to
your advantage and deflect its force.
As someone born in the
Year of the Horse,
that's all I can say about my feelings,
nothing more xd
Even those born in the Year
of the Horse don't
understand horses~ This is quite a...
Fun experiences including Princess
Pig on the grassland
Riding on the grasslands
for a long time,
the kickstand still hurts a bit,
even though it seems like I was in Jordan.
They were supposed to
let us ride camels,
but I didn't. I just played around with them
for a bit and didn't ride any camels.
You are not a horse, so why do you think
a horse is tired? (An ancient saying?)
The horse is currently
training for "King
of the Mountains"!
Charging upwards!
This is also a hiking trip,
but the sand here is just sand,
nothing special.
There are stairs,
but wait a moment (to reach
the horse parking area).
We're going up here now.
Keliro's name is too hard to pronounce
(so the guides all pronounce it Keliro).
It's called the Bromo
Crater of Mount Krelu.
Because you see it's
relatively short here,
but it should be quite large.
You can see the jets of air above.
The entire landscape is a spectacular
volcanic formation.
The tour guide said the most
difficult part of today's
hike was the approximately 200
-250 steps.
It's like building a staircase
on this volcanic terrain,
so you can...
I don't know why I was so short of
breath when I got to the crater today.
We're heading towards
the volcano now,
it seems like the Taipei
101 climbing race.
This is roughly equivalent
to the panting
level after climbing
about ten floors xd
(Super spectacular!!) An active
volcano that keeps erupting,
and then...
What you see here is actually quite
spectacular; theoretically,
you could walk around it like this.
Theoretically, it seems possible to go
there because this won't lead to...
The road surface is too steep,
but it's walkable.
So most tourists come
up the stairs here and
see this thing that's
been erupting.
Its visibility must be like
this: it keeps spraying,
and the smoke keeps rising,
so everything looks foggy.
It's probably volcanic ash.
Did you see any other clouds? They're cold.
When you see other clouds,
the cold air will come
down to this location.
It's spraying like crazy
over there!! There's
nothing else to describe it.
.. it's just spraying!
It's quite surprising that it
doesn't have much of a smell;
I thought it would have a strong,
very unpleasant odor.
But actually,
it's okay that the
horse smells bad (XD)
(Here) 4000 meters and then it collapsed.
After it collapsed...
These small volcanoes have started
erupting again, so...
They say it formed the volcano
within a volcano,
Mount Muteleb.
The riding instructors around
the volcano's
edge were covered in horse hair.
Some people are allergic
to horsehair,
it's true! And it's not
just in Indonesian oil pits.
It's still the Indonesian
Moon World~ This place
is very similar to Moon World,
but because...
The wilderness guide said
that this area is a very,
very large volcano.
As I just mentioned,
this place was originally a
What happened after the volcano,
with a diameter of ten kilometers and a height of over four kilometers,
finally collapsed?
It's amazing that these
small volcanoes have grown.
So originally,
the entire volcanic cluster was like this;
these are what we would call ruins.
It wasn't something washed
down by lava; rather,
it was simply that the
terrain collapsed.
So this is what it looks like now.
There's actually an outer layer,
which is the outer perimeter of the volcano.
We're at the observation deck.
So we are now in that place.
Let's go inside the volcano
to see this volcanic
complex and take a
selfie with myself.
Tourists and locals are about equal,
so the locals
We'll also visit this place
to conclude today's
itinerary before heading
to Mount Ijen.
Surabaya, which is near
the city I most want to
visit, is the so
-called Surabaya in Indonesia.
Blue Volcano Fried
Chicken (???)
(Me? Am I really that good at
mountain climbing?) They...
We're getting fried chicken soon!
XDDD Because of the fried chicken!
(Someone's going to pick
this up later) Me???
Thankfully, my chicken is still here;
I've already put it away.
Where is it located? Do we need
to send a higher
-level vehicle?
Of the 99 peaks (100 mountains) at a high level,
I can only rank second.
99 went to pick it up
(99 went?) (Anyway,
I came in the end...)
Our photographer disappeared
after climbing up.
(We met some locals who offered
to take us to collect them.)
This is something I noticed
when I used my phone
to zoom in; it's a four
-cornered device.
It really was that far (and
we actually found it!).
This is surprisingly accurate (I
got this view unexpectedly).
Now, after retrieving the drone,
I unexpectedly
saw a magnificent view.
Everything over there is white,
like it's snowing.
Our dogs don't need
to walk by themselves.
Our dog's name is Ma
Zou XDDDD Slow down,
slow down (please him first).
Remember to touch this side after you
dismount; it will make him happy.
Thank you. Bye
-bye.
(Upon reaching an open area in the distance,
one can see the entire Keliro volcano.)
(Bromo continued to emit smoke) (This
is not a prohibited scene...)
It's right at the
entrance; you can
see the volcano directly
and eat there.
(Somewhat like the fu in
Taitung) (Passing by the
largest thermal power
plant on Java Island)
Everyone, I woke up with my hair
sticking up and I was furious!
We've arrived at our
hotel around 3 PM now,
which is completely baffling.
Having a swimming pool is ridiculous
because we have to
go to Ijen Volcano very early tomorrow,
so today is...
We've reached a place close to Ijin,
but haven't arrived yet.
Because if they were to stay all
the way to the third floor today,
it would be too far, Bromo.
So, it's at a midpoint with Yi
-jin, therefore
I have to leave very early tomorrow,
at 12 o'clock, to continue my journey by bus.
I didn't actually take any pictures to show you.
Most of the time was spent hitchhiking
because of Indonesia.
This is really huge,
Java!
I should go to bed early
tonight because
I have to get up again at midnight.
(I find it absurd) But
that's how it is.
ROOM TOUR!
It's nice,
small and beautiful, and clean.
I'm not sure if it should be considered one.
It's a third
-tier city,
a small settlement,
not really a city, just a small settlement.
The feel of Taitung? We're
looking forward to tomorrow!
The blue flames of Ijen Volcano,
the dog dragging your luggage
at 11:30 tonight.
Li Xiang, check out here.
OK. The most important thing for this trip
is this sports protection capsule.
A slight illness followed
by overwork can
help improve one's
physical condition.
Magnesium is also important; I take
magnesium capsules after dinner.
What do you think of this
very special salty cookie?
Taiwanese people do have this kind of pancake
(it's a very sweet pancake!).
Too sweet, too sweet.
.. (Let's have dinner at the restaurant
downstairs in the hotel)
Hokkien fried noodles cost NT$35, which is roughly a serving for 2
-3 people...
(The four men ordered an enormous
amount of food...)
(Beef steak, steamed dumplings,
steamed buns, roast duck, oxtail soup)
The fried noodles were delicious,
and so was the oxtail soup.
Pizza Hut is getting ready to
go to sleep because I can only
sleep for four hours,
and there are some things outside.
We were very full from the Indonesian street
food and then prepared to go back.
Pack up and go to sleep
at 11:30 PM!! (Get up!)
Good morning everyone.
We're at the trailhead in Ijen now because
we're starting our ascent at 2 PM.
The control station doesn't
depart until 2 PM,
so we're preparing
to depart at 1:55 AM.
In Indonesia,
most people invest 5,000 rupiah,
so you should prepare some 5,000 rupiah banknotes.
We are currently at an altitude
of around 1900 meters,
and we plan to climb to 2400 meters.
The ascent is over 500 meters and 3.
7 kilometers; it says that's
a normal walking distance.
It takes about an hour and a half to walk slowly,
or if you walk fast...
It might only take an hour
to climb Mount Ijen.
The so
-called blue flame is one of only
two visible blue flames in the world.
One place is in Iceland,
and the other is in
The Ijen volcano in
Indonesia has been
talked about as a blue volcano...
Actually, it should be called Blue Flame,
the blue flame
they call it,
which comes from this Ijen volcano.
One of the volcanic
lakes formed inside
The guide will introduce the
blue flame to us later.
We really didn't do our research,
but it was...
I've known about this blue volcano for a very,
very long time.
I didn't know the blue
-flaming
volcano was called Mount Ijin.
The location is really very
close to Bali; it's
actually a 45
-minute boat ride to Bali on the right.
So if you want to visit Bali,
you can take a boat from here
and then go a little further.
You can go to Lombok and climb
a place called Mount Agung.
Join a volcano traverse
in Indonesia! (Remember
to bring a gas mask as the
air will be pungent.)
It looks like we're going to play Counter
-Strike (what a brat xd).
Guide: We should mainly follow their
(the local guides') instructions.
Let's take a group photo here
in Lamborghinis!!! (Locals say)
If you don't want to leave,
you can take this bulldozer that was converted.
A rickshaw (or pedicab?)
(A companion needed a
ride for filming!) We're
really off now!
(Two people pull from the front and push from the back,
an old man pushing a cart)
Rickshaws take up a lot of road space
(the Empress Dowager has arrived!).
Awesome! Awesome! Awesome!
(Laughs so hard,
the Chinese are really
good at teaching!)
bugatti bugatti bugatti oh~ (When
did it change to bugatti?)
Whatever kind of vehicle you need,
and what brand it is, we have it here!
It was quite steep (everyone took
off their coats except me).
This is seriously something
I could sleep
in; I want to sleep
away all my shame!!
There were seven rest stops in total,
and it was very chaotic because
there were just too many people.
So what I was originally going to
say was that this is very similar
to some kind of Hundred Peaks route,
it should be like...
I can't tell you the
route to Xiangshan.
So many people climbed 300 meters,
so it's only 200 meters more and we'll get there.
(Met Celine's fans!) Okay,
I've never been here before.
Bali feels a lot like climbing a
mountain in the dark in Taiwan.
Down...down...(Taking a bath)
Pineapple Custard Apple
It's so steep! (Guide: Remember
to stir it!!!) (So thoughtful!)
That guy who's really good at
hiking? (Found some weird snacks)
(A bit funny.
..) Filtering toxic gas
(There are a lot of people,
so remember to stick with your guide.)
She also wants to ride
in a Lamborghini!
(Laughing so hard) We've
now arrived at Hehuan North!
Hehuan North Peak is their
Lamborghini parking lot.
The main place is the Snow
Lord's Emerald Pool.
(Cut down from the mountaintop to the
volcanic lake to see the blue flames)
The road down is quite narrow,
so there are oncoming vehicles passing each other.
Sulfur Ore (Arrives
at Blue Flame)
(The flames will drip down,
so don't get too close.)
People were taking pictures
with this dying flame.
I was so touched (I just couldn't
stop crying).
(After watching the return journey) I
saw miners going up
and down the mine.
I can't take it back (because it's flammable
and can't be taken on the plane).
Back on the ridgeline,
the volcanic lake is much
larger than expected.
So now there's smoke
with sulfur in it,
which is a dream come true, right?
(Looking at the blue flame from
where the smoke was just now)
New Kangshan (it looks like the
New Kangtian Palace Fortress)
Everyone gathers here
to watch the sunrise.
It's said that this is the
real triangle spot of Yizhen,
and you can still smell a
faint sulfurous odor here.
Quite a few people still
wear that mask.
The summit is over 2700 meters
high; the triangulation
point should be at this location now.
The location is around 2300 meters,
but nobody climbs it because it's
not one of the Hundred Peaks.
Is it good or bad? Because I think this
place looks a lot like Jiaming Lake.
Sancha Mountain,
but because Sancha Mountain is one of the Hundred Peaks,
nobody goes there.
They said there was nothing you could do if you climbed to the top,
so nobody went.
Everyone's taking pictures of
Ijen's volcanic lake; the
volcanic lake is incredibly,
incredibly, incredibly blue.
As you can see,
this area is completely blue.
That's because sulfur reacts
with heat to produce...
Some high temperatures seem to indicate
that the temperature is
high enough, because not all volcanoes
have high temperatures.
Such a high flame requires
a very high temperature,
but just the right amount of heat is
obviously not noticeable to the body.
We can't feel how high
the temperature is.
They could get very close
to the blue flame,
but their previous experience
was relatively...
When it's at its most vigorous,
you can see the whole area.
The blue flame (slip of the tongue)
That trickle of little blue flame
A small piece on top and then
a small piece below, and
It's actually quite dangerous; you can't
get too close because of that...
The fire was probably quite hot,
and during filming, some falling rocks
(from the flames) also came down.
The bottom is the same hole
as the small oil pit.
These traces left by the sulfurous
(mountain walls) volcano
So the filming experience is actually
a bit similar to the Hundred
Peaks of Taiwan.
We just talked to the guide about this.
In other words, we all think the mountains
in Taiwan are very beautiful.
It's a pity that tourism
hasn't developed,
but I think it's unlikely because
we've been talking about...
This kind of culture allows people to go up
the mountain without restrictions; there
are even rickshaws available to transport
people to the first mountain in Taiwan.
It's impossible to pull a rickshaw
to the second altitude.
If you are really assuming the relationship
is based on Jiaming Lake
I certainly think that route
should be open for tourism.
The point is not a problem, but
Because the altitude is so high,
3300 meters, mountains are extremely prone to altitude sickness,
and the rescue efforts alone are a huge challenge.
It's possible that a bunch
of people will be carried off
the road along the way,
so don't talk about it going up.
A bunch of people were carried down,
so the mountains in Taiwan are still...
It's difficult to develop on a large
scale; the mountain roads are constantly
collapsing, and there isn't enough
space for residential areas.
Supply point,
wait a minute, let's mix it up.
We'll be heading down the
mountain soon. This time,
we'll have our usual meal.
Eggshell membrane from an Italian
pharmaceutical company,
which I have long recommended.
Protein nutrients extracted
using specialized techniques
There are a total of 500
kinds of nutrients that
are not usually easy
to obtain completely.
The benefits of consuming
this eggshell membrane
include improving your
mobility and activity.
More flexibility to
deal with these
Training, hiking in the mountains,
and volcano climbing trips
It contains 1500
mg of leucine.
Helps protein be used for muscle growth,
improves absorption and repair.
This thing is for dealing with
these overseas climbing trips.
For daily health maintenance,
take three capsules.
To maintain your health
and physical fitness,
even though the altitude
here isn't very high.
Make sure you get enough
physical conditioning
and sleep for the 2400
-meter race.
The suggestion is to
adjust your mindset
to the correct state
before setting off.
We need to be physically
fit and mentally
prepared to deal with
these challenges.
Natural wilderness trip,
Italian pharmaceutical company Ivylink,
Guan Jiejili
I recommend using it for
daily health maintenance.
This trip also used DJB.
In the context of using eSIM
for network connectivity
in a country as large as Java,
I think...
It seems there was only a short
stretch of road without signal.
All others have very strong signals,
with at least two bars.
So finding information is quite fast,
I recommend it to everyone, and the all
-you-can-eat option is still affordable.
For clothing selection,
it's recommended to use lightweight to medium
-weight down jackets for the base layer, preferably wool.
Don't go too thick,
then add a Polartec Alpha mid
-layer layer.
The shoes are just regular
hiking boots,
trail running shoes,
and trekking shoes.
Actually, a 20 or 25L
backpack is fine.
No need to bring a large
backpack (pH value 0.
2-0.5)
And sometimes it can even be zero,
so its acidity is extremely strong.
(A student asked: When is it 0.
2 and when is it 0.5?)
(Gasping for breath
xd) To be continued!
It will probably be between
20 and 40 degrees Celsius.
Remember to subscribe! (More
to come in the next episode!)
Like this post to turn on
notifications (I noticed
someone is doing trail
running training!!!!)
Down the mountain chill,
let's go for a wild boar hunt!
Awesome!
Log out!
Approximately 10K (round trip)
6 hours and 16 minutes
Breakfast was served immediately
upon arrival (the man
whose legs went numb from the
long bus ride back...).
(Finally back in Surabaya
city) (I only found out
in Indonesia that Taiwan
has banned mangosteens)
(Street food in Surabaya) Soto Ayam
(Indonesian chicken soup) is one
of the five national dishes officially
recognized by Indonesia.
In Indonesian, "Soto" means soup,
and "Ayam" refers to chicken.
(Eating chicken soup with background music) Bakso (Indonesian meatball
noodle soup) is Indonesia's most representative national street
food. This dish is influenced by Chinese cuisine, and its name "Bakso"
comes from the Hokkien word for "meat floss".
Bakso is mainly composed of bouncy Indonesian meatballs paired with hot clear soup,
noodles, or rice noodles.
(I don't know what it is
when the egg crepe is rolled
up) (It looks like Indonesian
grilled corn from Taiwan)
I'm currently at the
airport in Surabaya,
preparing to return to Taiwan.
(Regarding the two volcanoes...)
The trip concluded successfully; everything
was handled by [organization name].
Wilderness Traveler Travel
Agency will handle the
arrangements and planning
because of Indonesia.
Java is so big that you definitely
need to hire a car.
It's difficult to charter
a car for that person,
so they chose this option.
The itinerary of a group tour is greatly
influenced by the location.
It's very compact, I think if you were to come alone,
it might be possible.
A method can still be found,
but it will take time.
If the trip is long,
or you need to hire a car yourself.
The timing of the entire arrangement,
including accommodation and meals,
was also very appropriate.
The food and accommodation were
excellent; just hop on the
bus without any worries,
and then head to the attractions.
Then we climbed the volcano.
The tour guides were very attentive
and explained everything to you.
Many things to note: meeting
place and time
Everything was explained very
clearly and reassuringly.
So I suggest you next time to the volcano
twin volcano of the blue volcano
For information on Bromo volcano,
you can refer to the itinerary
provided by Wilderness Travel.
For those planning a volcano trip,
it's advisable to ensure you're
physically fit beforehand.
Because although the altitude is not high,
around 2400 meters,
There was still a slight climb,
so that's all for
today's video.
I'm Hiker CP.
See you next time.
See you at the
volcano!
(Leucine is an essential amino acid with smaller
molecules that are more easily absorbed)
If you like my video,
feel free to watch (the smoke
in the air is quite pungent).
here